A Guide to the Tredegar Iron Works Records, 1801-1957
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Correspondence, Inletters, 1872-1957, Extent: 231.45 cu. ft. (656 boxes). (Box 205-860)
  - Subseries 2: Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Co., 1900-1957, Extent: 11.2 cu. ft. (32 boxes). (Box 762-793)
    - 1905 July-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 768:4)
    - 1905 July-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 768:5)
    - 1906 January-April (Box-folder 769:1)
    - 1906 January-April (see oversize) (Box-folder 769:2)
    - 1906 January-April (Box-folder 769:3)
    - 1906 January-April (see oversize) (Box-folder 769:4)
    - 1906 May-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 769:5)
    - 1906 May-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 770:1)
    - 1906 May-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 770:2)
    - 1906 May-September (Box-folder 770:3)
    - 1906 May-September (Box-folder 770:4)
    - 1907 July-1908 January (Box-folder 770:5)
    - 1907 July-1908 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 770:6)
    - 1907 July-1908 January (Box-folder 771:1)
    - 1907 July-1908 January (Box-folder 771:2)
    - 1907 July-1908 January (Box-folder 771:3)
    - 1910-1911 (Box-folder 771:4)
    - 1910-1911 (Box-folder 771:5)
    - 1910-1911 (Box-folder 771:6)
    - 1910-1911 (Box-folder 772:1)
    - 1910-1911 (see oversize) (Box-folder 772:2)
    - 1911-1912 (see oversize) (Box-folder 772:3)
    - 1911-1912 (see oversize) (Box-folder 772:4)
    - 1911-1912 (see oversize) (Box-folder 772:5)
    - 1911-1912 (see oversize) (Box-folder 773:1)
    - 1917-1918 (Box-folder 773:2)
    - 1917-1918 (see oversize) (Box-folder 773:3)
    - 1917-1918 (Box-folder 773:4)
    - 1917-1918 (see oversize) (Box-folder 773:5)
    - 1919-1920 March (Box-folder 773:6)
    - 1919-1920 March (Box-folder 774:1)
    - 1919-1920 March (Box-folder 774:2)
    - 1919-1920 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 774:3)
    - 1920 March-June (Box-folder 774:4)
    - 1920 March-June (Box-folder 774:5)
    - 1920 March-June (see oversize) (Box-folder 775:1)
    - 1920 March-June (Box-folder 775:2)
    - 1920 June-October (Box-folder 775:3)
    - 1920 June-October (Box-folder 775:4)
    - 1920 June-October (Box-folder 775:5)
    - 1920 June-October (Box-folder 775:6)
    - 1920 June-October (Box-folder 775:7)
    - 1920 June-October (Box-folder 776:1)
    - 1920 October-1921 March (Box-folder 776:2)
    - 1920 October-1921 March (Box-folder 776:3)
    - 1920 October-1921 March (Box-folder 776:4)
    - 1921 March-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 776:5)
    - 1921 March-September (Box-folder 777:1)
    - 1921 March-September (Box-folder 777:2)
    - 1921 March-September (Box-folder 777:3)
    - 1921 September-1922 June (Box-folder 777:4)
    - 1921 September-1922 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 777:5)
    - 1921 September-1922 June (Box-folder 777:6)
    - 1921 September-1922 June (Box-folder 778:1)
    - 1922 June-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 778:2)
    - 1922 June-September (Box-folder 778:3)
    - 1922 June-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 778:4)
    - 1922 June-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 778:5)
    - 1922 June-September (Box-folder 778:6)
    - 1922 September-1923 April (Box-folder 779:1)
    - 1922 September-1923 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 779:2)
    - 1922 September-1923 April (Box-folder 779:3)
    - 1922 September-1923 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 779:4)
    - 1922 September-1923 April (Box-folder 779:5)
    - 1922 September-1923 April (Box-folder 779:6)
    - 1923 April-August (Box-folder 780:1)
    - 1923 April-August (Box-folder 780:2)
    - 1923 April-August (Box-folder 780:3)
    - 1923 August-December (Box-folder 780:4)
    - 1923 August-December (Box-folder 780:5)
    - 1923 August-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 780:6)
    - 1923 August-December (Box-folder 781:1)
    - 1923 August-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 781:2)
    - 1923 December-1924 May (Box-folder 781:3)
    - 1923 December-1924 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 781:4)
    - 1923 December-1924 May (Box-folder 781:5)
    - 1923 December-1924 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 781:6)
    - 1924 May-September (Box-folder 782:1)
    - 1924 May-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 782:2)
    - 1924 May-September (Box-folder 782:3)
    - 1924 May-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 782:4)
    - 1924 September-1925 March (Box-folder 782:5)
    - 1924 September-1925 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 782:6)
    - 1924 September-1925 March (Box-folder 783:1)
    - 1924 September-1925 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 783:2)
    - 1925 March-August (Box-folder 783:3)
    - 1925 March-August (Box-folder 783:4)
    - 1925 March-August (Box-folder 783:5)
    - 1925 March-August (see oversize) (Box-folder 783:6)
    - 1925 August-1926 January (Box-folder 784:1)
    - 1925 August-1926 January (Box-folder 784:2)
    - 1925 August-1926 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 784:3)
    - 1926 January-June (see oversize) (Box-folder 784:4)
    - 1926 January-June (Box-folder 784:5)
    - 1926 January-June (Box-folder 785:1)
    - 1926 June-November (Box-folder 785:2)
    - 1926 June-November (see oversize) (Box-folder 785:3)
    - 1926 June-November (Box-folder 785:4)
    - 1926 June-November (Box-folder 785:5)
    - 1926 November-1927 August (Box-folder 785:6)
    - 1926 November-1927 August (Box-folder 786:1)
    - 1926 November-1927 August (Box-folder 786:2)
    - 1926 November-1927 August (Box-folder 786:3)
    - 1927 August-1928 March (Box-folder 786:4)
    - 1927 August-1928 March (Box-folder 786:5)
    - 1927 August-1928 March (Box-folder 787:1)
    - 1927 August-1928 March (Box-folder 787:2)
    - 1928 March-October (Box-folder 787:3)
    - 1928 March-October (see oversize) (Box-folder 787:4)
    - 1928 March-October (Box-folder 787:5)
    - 1928 March-October (Box-folder 787:6)
    - 1928 October-1930 February (Box-folder 788:1)
    - 1928 October-1930 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 788:2)
    - 1928 October-1930 February (Box-folder 788:3)
    - 1928 October-1930 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 788:4)
    - 1930 February-1931 November (Box-folder 788:5)
    - 1930 February-1931 November (Box-folder 788:6)
    - 1930 February-1931 November (Box-folder 789:1)
    - 1930 February-1931 November (see oversize) (Box-folder 789:2)
    - 1931 November-1934 May (Box-folder 789:3)
    - 1931 November-1934 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 789:4)
    - 1931 November-1934 May (Box-folder 789:5)
    - 1931 November-1934 May (Box-folder 789:6)
    - 1934 May-1937 January (Box-folder 790:1)
    - 1934 May-1937 January (Box-folder 790:2)
    - 1934 May-1937 January (Box-folder 790:3)
    - 1934 May-1937 January (Box-folder 790:4)
    - 1943 March-1944 July (Box-folder 790:5)
    - 1943 March-1944 July (Box-folder 790:6)
    - 1943 March-1944 July (Box-folder 791:1)
    - 1944 July-1946 May (Box-folder 791:2)
    - 1944 July-1946 May (Box-folder 791:3)
    - 1944 July-1946 May (Box-folder 791:4)
    - 1944 July-1946 May (Box-folder 791:5)
    - 1946 May-1949 January (Box-folder 791:6)
    - 1946 May-1949 January (Box-folder 791:7)
    - 1946 May-1949 January (Box-folder 792:1)
    - 1946 May-1949 January (Box-folder 792:2)
    - 1949 January-1953 August (Box-folder 792:3)
    - 1949 January-1953 August (Box-folder 792:4)
    - 1949 January-1953 August (Box-folder 792:5)
    - 1949 January-1953 August (Box-folder 792:6)
    - 1953 August-1957 (Box-folder 793:1)
    - 1953 August-1957 (Box-folder 793:2)
  - Subseries 3: A.J. Beatty, 1910-1915, Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 794)
    - 1910 August-December (Box-folder 794:1)
    - 1911 January-March (Box-folder 794:2)
    - 1911 April-July (Box-folder 794:3)
    - 1914 September-1915 January (Box-folder 794:4)
    - 1915 February-August (Box-folder 794:5)
  - Subseries 4: Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1905-1956, Extent: 7.15 cu. ft. (17 boxes). (Box 794a-810)
    - 1905 June-1906 August (Box-folder 794a:1)
    - 1905 June-1906 August (see oversize) (Box-folder 794a:2)
    - 1905 June-1906 August (Box-folder 794a:3)
    - 1905 June-1906 August (Box-folder 794a:4)
    - 1911-1912 (Box-folder 795:1)
    - 1911-1912 (see oversize) (Box-folder 795:2)
    - 1911-1912 (Box-folder 795:3)
    - 1912-1914 (Box-folder 795:4)
    - 1912-1914 (see oversize) (Box-folder 795:5)
    - 1912-1914 (Box-folder 796:1)
    - 1912-1914 (see oversize) (Box-folder 796:2)
    - 1917-1918 (Box-folder 796:3)
    - 1917-1918 (Box-folder 796:4)
    - 1917-1918 (Box-folder 796:5)
    - 1917-1918 (Box-folder 796:6)
    - 1919 February-November (Box-folder 797:1)
    - 1919 February-November (Box-folder 797:2)
    - 1919 February-November (Box-folder 797:3)
    - 1919 February-November (Box-folder 797:4)
    - 1919 December-1920 June (Box-folder 797:5)
    - 1919 December-1920 June (Box-folder 797:6)
    - 1920 January-June (Box-folder 797:7)
    - 1920 June-1921 March (Box-folder 798:1)
    - 1920 June-1921 March (Box-folder 798:2)
    - 1920 June-1921 March (Box-folder 798:3)
    - 1920 June-1921 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 798:4)
    - 1921 March-October (Box-folder 798:5)
    - 1921 March-October (Box-folder 798:6)
    - 1921 March-October (Box-folder 799:1)
    - 1921 March-October (see oversize) (Box-folder 799:2)
    - 1921 October-1922 January (Box-folder 799:3)
    - 1921 October-1922 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 799:4)
    - 1921 October-1922 January (Box-folder 799:5)
    - 1921 October-1922 January (Box-folder 799:6)
    - 1922 January-May (Box-folder 800:1)
    - 1922 January-May (Box-folder 800:2)
    - 1922 January-May (Box-folder 800:3)
    - 1922 January-May (Box-folder 800:4)
    - 1922 May-September (Box-folder 800:5)
    - 1922 May-September (Box-folder 800:6)
    - 1922 May-September (Box-folder 801:1)
    - 1922 May-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 801:2)
    - 1922 May-September (Box-folder 801:3)
    - 1922 September-1923 January (Box-folder 801:4)
    - 1922 September-1923 January (Box-folder 801:5)
    - 1923 January-April (Box-folder 802:1)
    - 1923 January-April (Box-folder 802:2)
    - 1923 January-April (Box-folder 802:3)
    - 1923 January-April (Box-folder 802:4)
    - 1923 April-June (Box-folder 802:5)
    - 1923 April-June (Box-folder 803:1)
    - 1923 April-June (Box-folder 803:2)
    - 1923 June-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 803:3)
    - 1923 June-December (Box-folder 803:4)
    - 1923 June-December (Box-folder 803:5)
    - 1923 June-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 803:6)
    - 1923 December-1924 September (see oversize) (Box-folder 804:1)
    - 1923 December-1924 September (Box-folder 804:2)
    - 1923 December-1924 September (Box-folder 804:3)
    - 1923 December-1924 September (Box-folder 804:4)
    - 1924 September-1925 August (Box-folder 804:5)
    - 1924 September-1925 August (Box-folder 805:1)
    - 1924 September-1925 August (see oversize) (Box-folder 805:2)
    - 1925 August-1926 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 805:3)
    - 1925 August-1926 June (Box-folder 805:4)
    - 1925 August-1926 June (Box-folder 805:5)
    - 1926 June-1928 October (Box-folder 806:1)
    - 1926 June-1928 October (see oversize) (Box-folder 806:2)
    - 1926 June-1928 October (Box-folder 806:3)
    - 1928 October-1930 May (Box-folder 806:4)
    - 1928 October-1930 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 806:5)
    - 1928 October-1930 May (Box-folder 806:6)
    - 1928 October-1930 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 807:1)
    - 1930 May-1934 February (Box-folder 807:2)
    - 1930 May-1934 February (Box-folder 807:3)
    - 1930 May-1934 February (Box-folder 807:4)
    - 1934 February-1937 January (Box-folder 807:5)
    - 1934 February-1937 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 807:6)
    - 1934 February-1937 January (Box-folder 808:1)
    - 1937 January-1939 July (Box-folder 808:2)
    - 1937 January-1939 July (Box-folder 808:3)
    - 1937 January-1939 July (Box-folder 808:4)
    - 1939 July-1941 October (Box-folder 808:5)
    - 1939 July-1941 October (Box-folder 808:6)
    - 1939 July-1941 October (Box-folder 809:1)
    - 1941 October-1944 February (Box-folder 809:2)
    - 1941 October-1944 February (Box-folder 809:3)
    - 1941 October-1944 February (Box-folder 809:4)
    - 1941 October-1944 February (Box-folder 809:5)
    - 1944 February-1947 January (Box-folder 809:6)
    - 1944 February-1947 January (Box-folder 810:1)
    - 1944 February-1947 January (Box-folder 810:2)
    - 1944 February-1947 January (Box-folder 810:3)
    - 1947-1957 (Box-folder 810:4)
    - 1947-1957 (Box-folder 810:5)
    - 1947-1957 (Box-folder 810:6)
  - Subseries 5: Christian, Barton & Parker, 1930-1937, Extent: .45 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 811)
    - 1930-1937 (Box-folder 811:1)
    - 1930-1937 (Box-folder 811:2)
    - 1930-1937 (Box-folder 811:3)
    - 1930-1937 (Box-folder 811:4)
    - 1930-1937 (Box-folder 811:5)
  - Subseries 6: George Layman and Others, 1909-1948, Extent: .70 cu. ft (2 boxes). (Box 812-813)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 812:1)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 812:2)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 812:3)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 812:4)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 812:5)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 812:6)
    - 1909-1948 (Box-folder 813:1)
    - 1909-1948 (see oversize) (Box-folder 813:2)
  - Subseries 7: The Rail Joint Company and Poor & Company, 1925-1956, Extent: 8.4 cu. ft (24 boxes). (Box 814-837)
    - 1925 May-1926 March (Box-folder 814:1)
    - 1925 May-1926 March (Box-folder 814:2)
    - 1925 May-1926 March (Box-folder 814:3)
    - 1925 May-1926 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 814:4)
    - 1926 March-September (Box-folder 814:5)
    - 1926 March-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 815:1)
    - 1926 March-September (Box-folder 815:2)
    - 1926 September-1927 May (Box-folder 815:3)
    - 1926 September-1927 May (Box-folder 815:4)
    - 1926 September-1927 May (Box-folder 815:5)
    - 1927 May-1928 July (Box-folder 816:1)
    - 1927 May-1928 July (Box-folder 816:2)
    - 1927 May-1928 July (Box-folder 816:3)
    - 1927 May-1928 July (Box-folder 816:4)
    - 1928 July-1929 February (Box-folder 816:5)
    - 1928 July-1929 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 817:1)
    - 1929 February-November (see oversize) (Box-folder 817:2)
    - 1929 February-November (Box-folder 817:3)
    - 1929 February-November (Box-folder 817:4)
    - 1929 November-1930 October (see oversize) (Box-folder 817:5)
    - 1929 November-1930 October (Box-folder 818:1)
    - 1929 November-1930 October (Box-folder 818:2)
    - 1929 November-1930 October (Box-folder 818:3)
    - 1930 October-1931 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 818:4)
    - 1930 October-1931 June (Box-folder 818:5)
    - 1930 October-1931 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 818:6)
    - 1931 June-1932 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 819:1)
    - 1931 June-1932 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 819:2)
    - 1931 June-1932 April (Box-folder 819:3)
    - 1932 April-1933 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 819:4)
    - 1932 April-1933 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 819:5)
    - 1932 April-1933 June (Box-folder 819:6)
    - 1933 June-1934 January (Box-folder 820:1)
    - 1933 June-1934 January (Box-folder 820:2)
    - 1934 January-June (Box-folder 820:3)
    - 1934 January-June (Box-folder 820:4)
    - 1934 January-June (Box-folder 820:5)
    - 1934 June-1935 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 821:1)
    - 1934 June-1935 January (Box-folder 821:2)
    - 1934 June-1935 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 821:3)
    - 1935 January-November (see oversize) (Box-folder 821:4)
    - 1935 January-November (see oversize) (Box-folder 821:5)
    - 1935 January-November (see oversize) (Box-folder 821:6)
    - 1935 November-1936 July (see oversize) (Box-folder 822:1)
    - 1935 November-1936 July (see oversize) (Box-folder 822:2)
    - 1935 November-1936 July (Box-folder 822:3)
    - 1936 July-1937 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 822:4)
    - 1936 July-1937 January (Box-folder 822:5)
    - 1936 July-1937 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 822:6)
    - 1937 January-August (Box-folder 823:1)
    - 1937 January-August (see oversize) (Box-folder 823:2)
    - 1937 January-August (see oversize) (Box-folder 823:3)
    - 1937 August-1938 July (Box-folder 823:4)
    - 1937 August-1938 July (Box-folder 823:5)
    - 1937 August-1938 July (Box-folder 823:6)
    - 1938 July-1939 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 824:1)
    - 1938 July-1939 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 824:2)
    - 1938 July-1939 April (see oversize) (Box-folder 824:3)
    - 1939 April-August (see oversize) (Box-folder 824:4)
    - 1939 April-August (Box-folder 824:5)
    - 1939 April-August (Box-folder 824:6)
    - 1939 August-1940 February (Box-folder 825:1)
    - 1939 August-1940 February (Box-folder 825:2)
    - 1939 August-1940 February (Box-folder 825:3)
    - 1940 February-July (Box-folder 825:4)
    - 1940 February-July (Box-folder 825:5)
    - 1940 February-July (Box-folder 825:6)
    - 1940 July-1941 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 826:1)
    - 1940 July-1941 March (Box-folder 826:2)
    - 1940 July-1941 March (Box-folder 826:3)
    - 1941 March-September (see oversize) (Box-folder 826:4)
    - 1941 March-September (Box-folder 826:5)
    - 1941 March-September (Box-folder 827:1)
    - 1941 September-1942 March (Box-folder 827:2)
    - 1941 September-1942 March (Box-folder 827:3)
    - 1941 September-1942 March (Box-folder 827:4)
    - 1941 September-1942 March (Box-folder 827:5)
    - 1942 March-1943 March (Box-folder 828:1)
    - 1942 March-1943 March (Box-folder 828:2)
    - 1942 March-1943 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 828:3)
    - 1943 March-1944 July (see oversize) (Box-folder 828:4)
    - 1943 March-1944 July (Box-folder 828:5)
    - 1943 March-1944 July (Box-folder 829:1)
    - 1946 January-1947 February (Box-folder 829:2)
    - 1946 January-1947 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 829:3)
    - 1946 January-1947 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 829:4)
    - 1947 March-December (Box-folder 829:5)
    - 1947 March-December (Box-folder 830:1)
    - 1947 March-December (Box-folder 830:2)
    - 1948 January-August (see oversize) (Box-folder 830:3)
    - 1948 January-August (Box-folder 830:4)
    - 1948 January-August (Box-folder 830:5)
    - 1948 September-1949 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 831:1)
    - 1948 September-1949 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 831:2)
    - 1948 September-1949 March (see oversize) (Box-folder 831:3)
    - 1949 April-1950 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 831:4)
    - 1949 April-1950 February (see oversize) (Box-folder 831:5)
    - 1949 April-1950 February (Box-folder 832:1)
    - 1950 February-July (see oversize) (Box-folder 832:2)
    - 1950 February-July (see oversize) (Box-folder 832:3)
    - 1950 February-July (see oversize) (Box-folder 832:4)
    - 1950 July-December (Box-folder 832:5)
    - 1950 July-December (Box-folder 833:1)
    - 1950 July-December (Box-folder 833:2)
    - 1950 July-December (Box-folder 833:3)
    - 1951 January-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 833:4)
    - 1951 January-December (see oversize) (Box-folder 833:5)
    - 1951 January-December (Box-folder 834:1)
    - 1952 January-October (Box-folder 834:2)
    - 1952 January-October (Box-folder 834:3)
    - 1952 January-October (Box-folder 834:4)
    - 1952 January-October (Box-folder 834:5)
    - 1952 October-1953 September (Box-folder 834:6)
    - 1952 October-1953 September (Box-folder 835:1)
    - 1952 October-1953 September (Box-folder 835:2)
    - 1952 October-1953 September (Box-folder 835:3)
    - 1953 September-1954 August (Box-folder 835:4)
    - 1953 September-1954 August (Box-folder 835:5)
    - 1953 September-1954 August (Box-folder 835:6)
    - 1953 September-1954 August (see oversize) (Box-folder 836:1)
    - 1954 August-1955 November (Box-folder 836:2)
    - 1954 August-1955 November (Box-folder 836:3)
    - 1954 August-1955 November (see oversize) (Box-folder 836:4)
    - 1954 August-1955 November (Box-folder 836:5)
    - 1955 November-1956 October (Box-folder 836:6)
    - 1955 November-1956 October (Box-folder 837:1)
    - 1955 November-1956 October (see oversize) (Box-folder 837:2)
    - 1955 November-1956 October (Box-folder 837:3)
    - 1956 October-1957 June (Box-folder 837:4)
    - 1956 October-1957 June (Box-folder 837:5)
    - 1956 October-1957 June (Box-folder 837:6)
    - 1956 October-1957 June (Box-folder 837:7)
  - Subseries 8: Southern Railway Company, 1901-1957, Extent: 5.0 cu. ft (14 boxes). (Box 838-851)
    - 1901 November-1902 March (Box-folder 838:1)
    - 1901 November-1902 March (Box-folder 838:2)
    - 1902 March-June (Box-folder 838:3)
    - 1902 March-June (see oversize) (Box-folder 838:4)
    - 1902 March-June (Box-folder 838:5)
    - 1902 June-December (Box-folder 839:1)
    - 1902 June-December (Box-folder 839:2)
    - 1902 June-December (Box-folder 839:3)
    - 1902 June-December (Box-folder 839:4)
    - 1903 January-June (Box-folder 839:5)
    - 1903 January-June (Box-folder 840:1)
    - 1903 January-June (Box-folder 840:2)
    - 1903 June-November (Box-folder 840:3)
    - 1903 June-November (Box-folder 840:4)
    - 1903 June-November (Box-folder 840:5)
    - 1903 November-1904 May (Box-folder 841:1)
    - 1903 November-1904 May (Box-folder 841:2)
    - 1903 November-1904 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 841:3)
    - 1905 January-August (Box-folder 841:4)
    - 1905 January-August (Box-folder 842:1)
    - 1905 January-August (Box-folder 842:2)
    - 1905 August-1906 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 842:3)
    - 1905 August-1906 May (Box-folder 842:4)
    - 1905 August-1906 May (Box-folder 842:5)
    - 1917 March-1918 May (Box-folder 843:1)
    - 1917 March-1918 May (Box-folder 843:2)
    - 1917 March-1918 May (see oversize) (Box-folder 843:3)
    - 1918 May-1919 April (Box-folder 843:4)
    - 1918 May-1919 April (Box-folder 843:5)
    - 1918 May-1919 April (Box-folder 844:1)
    - 1919 April-1920 June (see oversize) (Box-folder 844:2)
    - 1919 April-1920 June (Box-folder 844:3)
    - 1919 April-1920 June (Box-folder 844:4)
    - 1920 June-1921 September (Box-folder 844:5)
    - 1920 June-1921 September (Box-folder 844:6)
    - 1920 June-1921 September (see oversize) (Box-folder 845:1)
    - 1920 June-1921 September (Box-folder 845:2)
    - 1921 September-1922 November (Box-folder 845:3)
    - 1921 September-1922 November (Box-folder 845:4)
    - 1922 November-1923 August (Box-folder 845:5)
    - 1922 November-1923 August (Box-folder 846:1)
    - 1922 November-1923 August (Box-folder 846:2)
    - 1922 November-1923 August (Box-folder 846:3)
    - 1923 August-1924 May (Box-folder 846:4)
    - 1923 August-1924 May (Box-folder 846:5)
    - 1923 August-1924 May (Box-folder 846:6)
    - 1923 August-1924 May (Box-folder 847:1)
    - 1924 May-1925 August (Box-folder 847:2)
    - 1924 May-1925 August (Box-folder 847:3)
    - 1924 May-1925 August (Box-folder 847:4)
    - 1925 August-1926 November (Box-folder 847:5)
    - 1925 August-1926 November (Box-folder 848:1)
    - 1925 August-1926 November (Box-folder 848:2)
    - 1926 November-1929 August (Box-folder 848:3)
    - 1926 November-1929 August (Box-folder 848:4)
    - 1926 November-1929 August (Box-folder 848:5)
    - 1929 August-1932 November (see oversize) (Box-folder 849:1)
    - 1929 August-1932 November (Box-folder 849:2)
    - 1932 November-1937 January (Box-folder 849:3)
    - 1932 November-1937 January (see oversize) (Box-folder 849:4)
    - 1932 November-1937 January (Box-folder 849:5)
    - 1937 January-1940 July (Box-folder 850:1)
    - 1937 January-1940 July (Box-folder 850:2)
    - 1937 January-1940 July (Box-folder 850:3)
    - 1940 July-1946 January (Box-folder 850:4)
    - 1940 July-1946 January (Box-folder 850:5)
    - 1940 July-1946 January (Box-folder 850:6)
    - 1946 January-1954 May (Box-folder 851:1)
    - 1946 January-1954 May (Box-folder 851:2)
    - 1946 January-1954 May (Box-folder 851:3)
    - 1946 January-1954 May (Box-folder 851:4)
    - 1954-1957 (Box-folder 851:5)
    - 1954-1957 (Box-folder 851:6)